nphoto.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy

Nphoto (“Nphoto”, “us” or “we”) respects the privacy of the visitors to its Website, the homepage of which is located at [www.nphoto.com](http://www.nphoto.com/) (“Website”) This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Website. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms set forth in the nPhoto Terms and Conditions that you can find at Terms and Conditions and which incorporate this Privacy Policy by reference.

“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. “Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy.  

**USER CONSENT**

By submitting Personal Information through our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

Your Personal Information may be processed by nPhoto in the country where it was collected as well as transferred to and processed in other countries (including Poland) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The Personal Information we gather from you helps us learn about visitors to the Website, our customers, and potential customers. We use this information to provide the Services to you, to better tailor the features, performance, and support of our products and services, and to offer you additional information and opportunities.

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website. When you register on the Website, we will collect your full name and username, a password, and an email address.

When you create your profile on the Website after registering, we will collect on an optional basis other Personal Information, such as hobbies, interests, additional contact information, etc.

When you order products or services on the Website, we will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information, and shipping information.

When you subscribe to a nPhoto newsletter, we will collect your email address.

When you contact us to submit comments, questions or feedback using the forms on the Website, we will collect your name, email address, and your comment, question or feedback.

When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information.

When you contact us using the request forms on the Website, we will collect your name, email address and your comment or question that you enter into the form.

When you post messages on the message boards of the Website, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it.

When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email address and any information contained in the email you send us and any information attached to the email.

Please note that Content that you use for your Products or that you contribute to other Members for their Products might also contain Personal Information. Please be mindful that such Content may be made available to others (including through the use of the Product’s preview functionality) as content of your Products or the Products of other Members to which you contributed Content and that you, therefore, should only use and contribute Content that you are comfortable sharing under these conditions.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED VIA TECHNOLOGY  **

As you navigate our Website, certain information may also be passively collected, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, domain names, access times, operating system, mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. This type of information is collected to analyze the use of our services and solutions and to make them more useful to you. Like other aspects of our services, we use a third party service provider for some or all of this type of data collection and analysis; these third-party service providers may also independently collect information about you as described in “Disclosure of Personal Information” below.

An “Internet protocol address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track IP Addresses solely in conjunction with session cookies to analyze our web page flow.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website or App. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website or App may not work properly.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM OTHER SOURCES**  

nPhoto execute and use display advertising. We implemented The Google Analytics features to display advertising (e.g., Remarketing). Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.

We applied additional marketing options of Google Analytics. They allow to collect such data as interest and demographic information.

Some fields of the web page may use cookies. They are used to identify the computer and help to simplify or cancel a particular action. They are not harmful to software or computer. Cookies work only if a user accepts them and does not remove them from the computer.

Personal details of our customers, collected with the help of cookies, are not being accessible to the third parties;

In order to prevent from saving cookie files on a computer, it is possible to resign from them or to turn them off, using the web browser. It is worthwhile taking into account, that turning cookie files off can cause significant deterioration of the activity of both our website and other sites.

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources, telephone or fax or from companies that provide our services by way of a co-branded or private-labeled website (“Partner Companies”)

**USE OF INFORMATION**

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make or to aid us in serving you better. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with the nPhoto newsletters, surveys, or promotional emails regarding changes and upgrades to our products and services and for other marketing purposes of nPhoto or our partners, should you request to receive such communications from us.

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze request patterns and usage patterns so that we may enhance our products and services. Nphoto reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in its discretion.

**FEEDBACK**

If you provide feedback on any of our products and services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. Nphoto will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties and we will not disclose financial information that is part of your Personal Information unless you ask us to do so.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties to provide you with the products and services that we offer you through the Website. These third parties are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the products and services requested by nPhoto and are bound by confidentiality agreements with regard to their use of such information. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Information with our contractors and third party service providers for the sole purpose of providing products and services to you.

We may enter into co-branding or co-promotional agreements with third parties pursuant to which we may share Personal Information with such third parties. For example, we may enter into agreements with Partner Companies pursuant to which we provide the Partner Companies with a URL and a customer registration page co-branded with, or private labeled by, the Partner Companies, and the Partner Companies distributes and promotes the URL to its customers. A Partner Company may have access to Personal Information that we collect from their customers. As a result, if you register on the Website or App through a Partner Company, we may provide your Personal Information to the Partner Company. Please note, however, that we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties.

We use third-party advertising and/or web analytics companies to serve ads and/or to provide us web analytics when you visit our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites (e.g., through the use of cookies) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you, to provide us analyses of how our site is used. Although we do not authorize these third parties to collect your Personal Information from our Website, they may associate data collected about your use of our Website with the personally identifiable information they have collected about you from other websites.

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with companies under common control such as any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or parent company (collectively, “Affiliates”), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Information (as described below), we may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on nPhoto; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of nPhoto or users of our Services.

**YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Despite your indicated preferences, we may send you communications regarding the services we provide to you, such as transaction reports, notices about updates, notices of new Website or Program, and notices regarding changes to the Website or Program, updates to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or other policies.

You may change any of the Personal Information in your account by editing your online profile or by sending an email to us at the email address set forth below.

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

**SECURITY**

Nphoto is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

Nphoto has implemented industry-standard electronic means of protecting your Personal Information. We store Personal Information behind a computer firewall, a barrier designed to prevent outsiders from accessing our servers, and we have implemented technology to detect intrusions. We also require you to enter a password to access your account information. In addition, nPhoto protects your Personal Information from unauthorized physical access by storing your Personal Information in a controlled facility. Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, nPhoto limits access to Personal Information in electronic databases to those persons (including employees and contractors) in nPhoto’s organization who have a business need for such access. Lastly, we conduct periodic internal audits and vulnerability scans to ensure compliance with these security measures and generate security incident logs that track Information useful in screening for attempted abuse of or unauthorized access to your Personal Information.

Even though nPhoto has taken significant steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that nPhoto cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

This Privacy Statement is a living document. As part of the nPhoto Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy is subject to occasional amendment, in accordance with the terms of the Terms and Conditions.

Owner of the service:

Cyfrowa Foto Sp. z o.o.

Zaczernie 190

36-062 Zaczernie
